<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Park Guide</string>
    <string name="learnMore">Learn More</string>
    <string name="defaultParkTitle">Default park title</string>
    <string name="defaultParkDescription">Default park description</string>
    <string name="parkContentDescription">An image representing a park</string>
    <string name="stateFlagContentDescription">An image representing a state flag</string>
    <string name="favoriteButton">Toggle favorite park</string>

    <string name="Alaska">Alaska</string>
    <string name="American_Samoa">American Samoa</string>
    <string name="Arizona">Arizona</string>
    <string name="Arkansas">Arkansas</string>
    <string name="California">California</string>
    <string name="Colorado">Colorado</string>
    <string name="Florida">Florida</string>
    <string name="Hawaii">Hawaii</string>
    <string name="Idaho">Idaho</string>
    <string name="Illinois">Illinois</string>
    <string name="Indiana">Indiana</string>
    <string name="Maine">Maine</string>
    <string name="Michigan">Michigan</string>
    <string name="Minnesota">Minnesota</string>
    <string name="Missouri">Missouri</string>
    <string name="Montana">Montana</string>
    <string name="Nevada">Nevada</string>
    <string name="New_Mexico">New Mexico</string>
    <string name="North_Carolina">North Carolina</string>
    <string name="North_Dakota">North Dakota</string>
    <string name="Ohio">Ohio</string>
    <string name="Oregon">Oregon</string>
    <string name="South_Carolina">South Carolina</string>
    <string name="South_Dakota">South Dakota</string>
    <string name="Tennessee">Tennessee</string>
    <string name="Texas">Texas</string>
    <string name="Utah">Utah</string>
    <string name="Virgin_Islands">Virgin Islands</string>
    <string name="Virginia">Virginia</string>
    <string name="Washington">Washington</string>
    <string name="West_Virginia">West Virginia</string>
    <string name="Wyoming">Wyoming</string>

    <string name="Acadia_National_Park">Acadia National Park</string>
    <string name="National_Park_of_American_Samoa">National Park of American Samoa</string>
    <string name="Arches_National_Park">Arches National Park</string>
    <string name="Badlands_National_Park">Badlands National Park</string>
    <string name="Big_Bend_National_Park">Big Bend National Park</string>
    <string name="Biscayne_National_Park">Biscayne National Park</string>
    <string name="Black_Canyon_of_the_Gunnison_National_Park">Black Canyon of the Gunnison National Park</string>
    <string name="Bryce_Canyon_National_Park">Bryce Canyon National Park</string>
    <string name="Canyonlands_National_Park">Canyonlands National Park</string>
    <string name="Capitol_Reef_National_Park">Capitol Reef National Park</string>
    <string name="Carlsbad_Caverns_National_Park">Carlsbad Caverns National Park</string>
    <string name="Channel_Islands_National_Park">Channel Islands National Park</string>
    <string name="Congaree_National_Park">Congaree National Park</string>
    <string name="Crater_Lake_National_Park">Crater Lake National Park</string>
    <string name="Cuyahoga_Valley_National_Park">Cuyahoga Valley National Park</string>
    <string name="Death_Valley_National_Park">Death Valley National Park</string>
    <string name="Denali_National_Park_and_Preserve">Denali National Park and Preserve</string>
    <string name="Dry_Tortugas_National_Park">Dry Tortugas National Park</string>
    <string name="Everglades_National_Park">Everglades National Park</string>
    <string name="Gates_of_the_Arctic_National_Park_and_Preserve">Gates of the Arctic National Park and Preserve</string>
    <string name="Gateway_Arch_National_Park">Gateway Arch National Park</string>
    <string name="Glacier_National_Park">Glacier National Park</string>
    <string name="Glacier_Bay_National_Park_and_Reserve">Glacier Bay National Park and Reserve</string>
    <string name="Grand_Canyon_National_Park">Grand Canyon National Park</string>
    <string name="Grand_Teton_National_Park">Grand Teton National Park</string>
    <string name="Great_Basin_National_Park">Great Basin National Park</string>
    <string name="Great_Sand_Dunes_National_Park_and_Reserve">Great Sand Dunes National Park and Preserve</string>
    <string name="Great_Smoky_Mountains_National_Park">Great Smoky Mountains National Park</string>
    <string name="Guadalupe_Mountains_National_Park">Guadalupe Mountains National Park</string>
    <string name="Haleakalā_National_Park">Haleakalā National Park</string>
    <string name="Hawaii_Volcanoes_National_Park">Hawai\'i Volcanoes National Park</string>
    <string name="Hot_Springs_National_Park">Hot Springs National Park</string>
    <string name="Indiana_Dunes_National_Park">Indiana Dunes National Park</string>
    <string name="Isle_Royale_National_Park">Isle Royale National Park</string>
    <string name="Joshua_Tree_National_Park_and_Preserve">Joshua Tree National Park and Preserve</string>
    <string name="Katmai_National_Park">Katmai National Park</string>
    <string name="Kenai_Fjords_National_Park">Kenai Fjords National Park</string>
    <string name="Kings_Canyon_National_Park">Kings Canyon National Park</string>
    <string name="Kobuk_Valley_National_Park">Kobuk Valley National Park</string>
    <string name="Lake_Clark_National_Park_and_Preserve">Lake Clark National Park and Preserve</string>
    <string name="Lassen_Volcanic_National_Park">Lassen Volcanic National Park</string>
    <string name="Mammoth_Cave_National_Park">Mammoth Cave National Park</string>
    <string name="Mesa_Verde_National_Park">Mesa Verde National Park</string>
    <string name="Mount_Rainier_National_Park">Mount Rainier National Park</string>
    <string name="New_River_Gorge_National_Park_and_Preserve">New River Gorge National Park and Preserve</string>
    <string name="North_Cascades_National_Park">North Cascades National Park</string>
    <string name="Olympic_National_Park">Olympic National Park</string>
    <string name="Petrified_Forest_National_Park">Petrified Forest National Park</string>
    <string name="Pinnacles_National_Park">Pinnacles National Park</string>
    <string name="Redwood_National_and_State_Parks">Redwood National and State Parks</string>
    <string name="Rocky_Mountain_National_Park">Rocky Mountain National Park</string>
    <string name="Saguaro_National_Park">Saguaro National Park</string>
    <string name="Sequoia_National_Park">Sequoia National Park</string>
    <string name="Shenandoah_National_Park">Shenandoah National Park</string>
    <string name="Theodore_Roosevelt_National_Park">Theodore Roosevelt National Park</string>
    <string name="Virgin_Islands_National_Park">Virgin Islands National Park</string>
    <string name="Voyageurs_National_Park">Voyageurs National Park</string>
    <string name="White_Sands_National_Park">White Sands National Park</string>
    <string name="Wind_Cave_National_Park">Wind Cave National Park</string>
    <string name="WrangellSt._Elias_National_Park_and_Preserve">Wrangell–St. Elias National Park and Preserve</string>
    <string name="Yellowstone_National_Park">Yellowstone National Park</string>
    <string name="Yosemite_National_Park">Yosemite National Park</string>
    <string name="Zion_National_Park">Zion National Park</string>

    <string name="Acadia_National_Park_Description">Acadia National Park, nestled along Maine\'s rugged coastline, features a diverse landscape of granite peaks, dense forests, and pristine lake shores. With over 120 miles of hiking trails and picturesque carriage roads, visitors can explore iconic landmarks like Cadillac Mountain and Jordan Pond while enjoying activities such as wildlife watching and ocean kayaking.</string>
    <string name="National_Park_of_American_Samoa_Description">The National Park of American Samoa, set amidst the South Pacific, offers a unique fusion of Polynesian culture and tropical ecosystems across three volcanic islands. Visitors can delve into lush rainforests, snorkel among vibrant coral reefs, and discover traditional Samoan villages, immersing themselves in the rich heritage and natural beauty of the archipelago.</string>
    <string name="Arches_National_Park_Description">Arches National Park in Utah showcases over 2,000 natural sandstone arches, sculpted by wind and water over millennia, against the stunning backdrop of the La Sal Mountains. With iconic landmarks like Delicate Arch and Balanced Rock, the park offers scenic hiking trails through breathtaking rock formations, providing visitors with an unforgettable experience of the desert landscape</string>
    <string name="Badlands_National_Park_Description">Badlands National Park, situated in South Dakota, presents a surreal landscape of rugged terrain, colorful rock formations, and expansive prairies. The park\'s unique geologic features, including buttes, pinnacles, and spires, provide a striking backdrop for outdoor adventures such as hiking, camping, and wildlife viewing. Visitors can explore ancient fossil beds, observe bison herds roaming the grasslands, and marvel at the dramatic sunsets painting the sky over the Badlands\' rugged beauty.</string>
    <string name="Big_Bend_National_Park_Description">Big Bend National Park, located in Texas along the Rio Grande, showcases a vast wilderness of desert landscapes, deep canyons, and towering mountains. Offering opportunities for hiking, river rafting, and stargazing in one of the darkest skies in the United States, Big Bend invites visitors to immerse themselves in its remote and rugged beauty. From the rugged Chisos Mountains to the tranquil banks of the Rio Grande, the park\'s diverse ecosystems support a wide array of plant and animal life, making it a haven for nature enthusiasts and adventurers alike.</string>
    <string name="Biscayne_National_Park_Description">Biscayne National Park, situated in southern Florida, encompasses a unique marine ecosystem of vibrant coral reefs, turquoise waters, and mangrove forests. Spanning the northernmost Florida Keys, the park offers opportunities for snorkeling, diving, and boating amid its pristine marine environment. With colorful coral gardens, seagrass meadows, and abundant marine life including manatees and sea turtles, Biscayne National Park provides a tranquil escape into the beauty and biodiversity of the underwater world.</string>
    <string name="Black_Canyon_of_the_Gunnison_National_Park_Description">Black Canyon of the Gunnison National Park, located in Colorado, is characterized by its sheer, dark cliffs plunging into the Gunnison River below. Visitors can marvel at the park\'s dramatic scenery from overlooks along the rim, hike challenging trails into the depths of the canyon, or enjoy scenic drives along the South Rim Road. With opportunities for rock climbing, wildlife viewing, and stargazing, Black Canyon of the Gunnison offers a rugged and awe-inspiring experience for outdoor enthusiasts.</string>
    <string name="Bryce_Canyon_National_Park_Description">Bryce Canyon National Park, nestled in southern Utah, is renowned for its unique geological formations known as hoodoos. These towering spires and amphitheaters create a surreal landscape of red and orange rock that changes hues with the shifting sunlight. Visitors can explore the park\'s scenic viewpoints, hike along trails that wind through the hoodoos, or admire the star-filled skies at night. With opportunities for horseback riding, photography, and ranger-led programs, Bryce Canyon offers a memorable experience in the heart of Utah\'s canyon country.</string>
    <string name="Canyonlands_National_Park_Description">Canyonlands National Park, also located in Utah, is a vast wilderness of canyons, mesas, and buttes carved by the Colorado River and its tributaries. Divided into four districts, each with its own distinct landscape and recreational opportunities, the park offers endless possibilities for exploration and adventure. Visitors can hike to iconic viewpoints, paddle through the remote canyons of the Green and Colorado Rivers, or embark on multi-day backpacking trips into the park\'s rugged backcountry. With its stunning vistas, rugged terrain, and sense of solitude, Canyonlands National Park provides a truly immersive experience in the beauty of the American Southwest.
    </string>
    <string name="Capitol_Reef_National_Park_Description">Capitol Reef National Park, situated in Utah, is a hidden gem characterized by its towering cliffs, colorful canyons, and unique geological formations. Visitors can drive the scenic Capitol Reef Scenic Drive to marvel at the park\'s stunning landscapes, hike along trails that wind through narrow slot canyons and past ancient petroglyphs, or explore the park\'s historic orchards and pioneer homesteads. With its rich history, diverse ecosystems, and breathtaking scenery, Capitol Reef offers a glimpse into the natural and cultural heritage of the American West.</string>
    <string name="Carlsbad_Caverns_National_Park_Description">Carlsbad Caverns National Park, located in New Mexico, is home to one of the largest cave systems in the world, featuring a network of over 100 caves carved out of limestone by sulfuric acid. Visitors can descend into the depths of the earth to explore the otherworldly formations of Carlsbad Cavern, hike along scenic trails in the surrounding Chihuahuan Desert, or witness the spectacular bat flights that occur at dusk during certain times of the year. With its fascinating geology, diverse wildlife, and underground wonders, Carlsbad Caverns offers an unforgettable adventure into the mysterious world below.</string>
    <string name="Channel_Islands_National_Park_Description">Channel Islands National Park, off the coast of Southern California, is a remote and pristine archipelago comprising five rugged islands and their surrounding waters. Accessible only by boat or plane, the park offers opportunities for hiking, camping, snorkeling, and wildlife viewing in a pristine coastal wilderness. Visitors can explore sea caves, kayak through kelp forests, and encounter diverse marine life, including seals, sea lions, and dolphins. With its unspoiled beauty and abundant biodiversity, Channel Islands National Park provides a tranquil escape from the hustle and bustle of mainland life.</string>
    <string name="Congaree_National_Park_Description">Congaree National Park, located in South Carolina, is home to one of the largest intact expanses of old-growth bottomland hardwood forest in the United States. Visitors can explore the park\'s lush forests via elevated boardwalks, paddle through its tranquil waters on canoe or kayak excursions, or embark on guided ranger-led programs to learn about the park\'s unique ecology and cultural history. With its towering trees, diverse wildlife, and scenic waterways, Congaree offers a peaceful retreat into the heart of nature.</string>
    <string name="Crater_Lake_National_Park_Description">Crater Lake National Park, nestled in the Cascade Mountains of Oregon, is renowned for its stunningly blue and crystal-clear lake, which fills the caldera of an ancient volcano. Visitors can admire panoramic views of the lake from scenic overlooks along Rim Drive, hike along trails that wind through old-growth forests and wildflower meadows, or take a boat tour to explore the lake\'s pristine waters up close. With its dramatic landscapes, diverse flora and fauna, and opportunities for outdoor recreation year-round, Crater Lake offers a truly unforgettable experience in the Pacific Northwest.</string>
    <string name="Cuyahoga_Valley_National_Park_Description">Cuyahoga Valley National Park, located in Ohio, preserves the rural landscape along the Cuyahoga River between Akron and Cleveland. Visitors can explore the park\'s scenic beauty by hiking or biking along the Ohio &amp; Erie Canal Towpath Trail, enjoying picnics in lush meadows, or taking scenic train rides through the valley. With its historic villages, cascading waterfalls, and diverse wildlife, Cuyahoga Valley offers a peaceful escape into nature just a short drive from urban centers.</string>
    <string name="Death_Valley_National_Park_Description">Death Valley National Park, situated in California and Nevada, is known for its extreme desert landscapes, including the lowest point in North America at Badwater Basin and the strikingly colorful badlands of Artist\'s Palette. Visitors can explore the park\'s diverse terrain, from vast salt flats to rugged mountains, and experience dramatic temperature variations, making it a unique and challenging destination for adventurers. With its iconic sand dunes, rugged canyons, and unique geological features, Death Valley offers a surreal and unforgettable experience in one of the hottest and driest places on Earth.</string>
    <string name="Denali_National_Park_and_Preserve_Description">Denali National Park and Preserve, located in Alaska, is home to North America\'s highest peak, Denali, towering at 20,310 feet. The park\'s vast wilderness encompasses six million acres of tundra, taiga, and snow-capped mountains, providing habitat for diverse wildlife, including grizzly bears, wolves, and moose. Visitors can explore the park\'s rugged terrain on bus tours, hiking trails, or backcountry expeditions, immersing themselves in the pristine beauty of the Alaskan wilderness. With its towering peaks, abundant wildlife, and unspoiled landscapes, Denali offers a truly epic adventure in the heart of the Last Frontier.</string>
    <string name="Dry_Tortugas_National_Park_Description">Dry Tortugas National Park, located off the coast of Florida, is a remote and pristine island chain known for its crystal-clear waters, coral reefs, and historic Fort Jefferson. Accessible only by boat or seaplane, the park offers opportunities for snorkeling, diving, birdwatching, and exploring the ruins of the 19th-century fort. With its secluded beaches, vibrant marine life, and rich history, Dry Tortugas provides a tranquil and secluded escape into the beauty of the tropical Caribbean.</string>
    <string name="Everglades_National_Park_Description">Everglades National Park, situated in southern Florida, is the largest tropical wilderness of any kind in the United States. Known as the "River of Grass," the park is home to a diverse array of plant and animal species, including alligators, manatees, and rare birds like the roseate spoonbill. Visitors can explore the park\'s unique ecosystems by hiking along boardwalk trails, paddling through mangrove forests and freshwater marshes, or taking guided boat tours to discover the wonders of this vast wetland wilderness. With its rich biodiversity, scenic landscapes, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, Everglades National Park offers an unforgettable adventure into one of the most unique and ecologically important ecosystems in the world.</string>
    <string name="Gates_of_the_Arctic_National_Park_and_Preserve_Description">Gates of the Arctic National Park and Preserve, located entirely above the Arctic Circle in Alaska, is one of the most remote and least-visited national parks in the United States. With no roads, trails, or visitor facilities, the park offers a true wilderness experience for those willing to venture into its rugged terrain. Visitors can explore pristine tundra, rugged mountains, and wild rivers, encountering abundant wildlife such as caribou, wolves, and grizzly bears along the way. With its vast expanses of untouched wilderness and sense of solitude, Gates of the Arctic provides a rare opportunity to experience the untamed beauty of the Arctic wilderness.</string>
    <string name="Gateway_Arch_National_Park_Description">Gateway Arch National Park, located in St. Louis, Missouri, preserves the iconic Gateway Arch, a symbol of America\'s westward expansion. Visitors can ride to the top of the arch for panoramic views of the city and the Mississippi River, explore the museum at the base of the arch to learn about the history of the American West, or stroll through the park\'s landscaped grounds and scenic riverfront. With its striking architecture, rich history, and central location in downtown St. Louis, Gateway Arch National Park offers a unique blend of culture, recreation, and natural beauty in the heart of the Midwest.</string>
    <string name="Glacier_National_Park_Description">Glacier National Park, located in Montana along the Canadian border, is known for its stunning alpine landscapes, glacier-carved valleys, and pristine wilderness. Visitors can explore over 700 miles of hiking trails, drive along the scenic Going-to-the-Sun Road for breathtaking views of glaciers and mountain peaks, or embark on scenic boat tours of the park\'s pristine lakes. With its diverse ecosystems, including dense forests, alpine meadows, and rugged peaks, Glacier National Park offers endless opportunities for outdoor recreation and awe-inspiring natural beauty.</string>
    <string name="Glacier_Bay_National_Park_and_Reserve_Description">Glacier Bay National Park and Preserve, situated in southeastern Alaska, is a pristine wilderness of fjords, glaciers, and temperate rainforests. Visitors can cruise through the park\'s icy waters to witness calving glaciers, spot humpback whales and sea otters, or hike along scenic trails to explore the park\'s diverse landscapes. With its remote and rugged beauty, Glacier Bay provides a unique opportunity to experience the wonders of the Alaskan wilderness in one of the most pristine and untouched environments in the world.</string>
    <string name="Grand_Canyon_National_Park_Description">Grand Canyon National Park, located in Arizona, is one of the most iconic natural wonders of the world, carved by the mighty Colorado River over millions of years. Visitors can marvel at the canyon\'s immense size and colorful rock formations from scenic overlooks along the South Rim or take a thrilling rafting trip through the canyon\'s rugged interior. With its sheer cliffs, deep gorges, and breathtaking vistas, Grand Canyon National Park offers an unforgettable adventure into the depths of one of the earth\'s most spectacular landscapes.</string>
    <string name="Grand_Teton_National_Park_Description">Grand Teton National Park, nestled in northwestern Wyoming, boasts majestic mountain peaks, pristine alpine lakes, and abundant wildlife. Visitors can explore the park\'s rugged terrain on hiking trails that lead to stunning viewpoints, go wildlife watching for elk, moose, and grizzly bears, or enjoy water activities such as boating and fishing on Jackson Lake. With its iconic Teton Range towering over the landscape, Grand Teton National Park offers a picturesque setting for outdoor adventures and scenic drives along the park\'s winding roads.</string>
    <string name="Great_Basin_National_Park_Description">Great Basin National Park, located in eastern Nevada, encompasses a diverse landscape of rugged mountains, ancient bristlecone pine forests, and expansive desert valleys. Visitors can explore the park\'s underground wonders in Lehman Caves, hike to the summit of Wheeler Peak for panoramic views of the surrounding desert, or stargaze under some of the darkest skies in the United States. With its unique geology, diverse ecosystems, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, Great Basin National Park offers a tranquil escape into the beauty of the American West.</string>
    <string name="Great_Sand_Dunes_National_Park_and_Reserve_Description">Great Sand Dunes National Park and Preserve, situated in southern Colorado, is home to the tallest sand dunes in North America, towering up to 750 feet high against the backdrop of the Sangre de Cristo Mountains. Visitors can hike on the dunes, splash in Medano Creek, or go sandboarding and sledding down the sandy slopes. With its dramatic landscapes, diverse wildlife, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, Great Sand Dunes National Park offers a unique and unforgettable experience in the heart of the Colorado Rockies.</string>
    <string name="Great_Smoky_Mountains_National_Park_Description">Great Smoky Mountains National Park, straddling the border of North Carolina and Tennessee, is renowned for its ancient mountains, lush forests, and rich biodiversity. Visitors can explore over 800 miles of hiking trails, drive along scenic mountain roads, or discover historic cabins and homesteads preserved within the park. With its stunning waterfalls, panoramic vistas, and diverse wildlife, Great Smoky Mountains National Park offers endless opportunities for outdoor adventure and scenic beauty in the heart of the Appalachian Mountains.</string>
    <string name="Guadalupe_Mountains_National_Park_Description">Guadalupe Mountains National Park, located in west Texas, showcases rugged desert landscapes, towering limestone peaks, and pristine wilderness. Visitors can hike to the summit of Guadalupe Peak, the highest point in Texas, explore ancient fossil reefs at McKittrick Canyon, or marvel at the park\'s stunning night skies. With its remote and rugged beauty, Guadalupe Mountains National Park provides a tranquil escape into the untamed wilderness of the Chihuahuan Desert.</string>
    <string name="Haleakalā_National_Park_Description">Haleakalā National Park, situated on the island of Maui in Hawaii, is home to the world\'s largest dormant volcano and a unique landscape of volcanic craters, lush rainforests, and subalpine ecosystems. Visitors can hike through the otherworldly landscapes of the summit area, explore the lush wilderness of the Kīpahulu District, or stargaze from one of the park\'s designated observation points. With its breathtaking vistas, diverse ecosystems, and cultural significance to the Hawaiian people, Haleakalā National Park offers a memorable experience of the natural and cultural heritage of the Hawaiian Islands.</string>
    <string name="Hawaii_Volcanoes_National_Park_Description">Hawai\'i Volcanoes National Park, located on the Big Island of Hawaii, showcases the dynamic landscapes shaped by volcanic activity, including active lava flows, steaming vents, and rugged lava fields. Visitors can explore the park\'s otherworldly terrain on scenic drives, hike along trails that lead to volcanic craters and lava tubes, or witness the spectacle of molten lava flowing into the ocean. With its dramatic geological features, diverse ecosystems, and cultural significance to the Hawaiian people, Hawai\'i Volcanoes National Park offers a captivating journey into the heart of the Pacific Ring of Fire.</string>
    <string name="Hot_Springs_National_Park_Description">Hot Springs National Park, nestled in the Ouachita Mountains of Arkansas, is renowned for its thermal springs, historic bathhouses, and lush forested landscapes. Visitors can soak in the healing waters of the park\'s thermal pools, explore the historic architecture of Bathhouse Row, or hike along scenic trails that wind through the park\'s rugged terrain. With its soothing waters, scenic beauty, and rich history dating back thousands of years, Hot Springs National Park offers a rejuvenating escape into the natural and cultural heritage of the American South.</string>
    <string name="Indiana_Dunes_National_Park_Description">Indiana Dunes National Park, located along the shores of Lake Michigan in Indiana, encompasses a diverse landscape of sand dunes, wetlands, and forests, providing habitat for a wide variety of plant and animal species. Visitors can explore the park\'s scenic beaches, hike along trails that traverse sand dunes and wooded ravines, or enjoy birdwatching and wildlife viewing in the park\'s diverse ecosystems. With its stunning natural beauty, recreational opportunities, and cultural significance as a haven for conservation and outdoor recreation, Indiana Dunes National Park offers a memorable experience along the shores of the Great Lakes.</string>
    <string name="Isle_Royale_National_Park_Description">Isle Royale National Park, located in Lake Superior off the coast of Michigan, is the largest island in the largest freshwater lake in the world. The park is known for its rugged wilderness, pristine forests, and abundant wildlife, including wolves, moose, and bald eagles. Visitors can explore the island\'s remote trails, paddle along its rocky shoreline, or embark on backcountry camping trips to experience the solitude and beauty of this remote wilderness. With its untouched landscapes and opportunities for outdoor adventure, Isle Royale National Park offers a truly wild and immersive experience in the heart of the Great Lakes.</string>
    <string name="Joshua_Tree_National_Park_and_Preserve_Description">Joshua Tree National Park, located in southern California, is renowned for its surreal landscapes of twisted Joshua trees, towering rock formations, and vast desert expanses. Visitors can hike along trails that wind through the park\'s unique ecosystems, rock climb on its iconic granite formations, or stargaze under its dark skies. With its otherworldly beauty and sense of solitude, Joshua Tree National Park offers a peaceful retreat into the stark beauty of the Mojave and Colorado Deserts.</string>
    <string name="Katmai_National_Park_Description">Katmai National Park, situated in southern Alaska, is home to some of the largest populations of brown bears in the world, as well as a spectacular landscape of rugged mountains, active volcanoes, and pristine wilderness. Visitors can observe bears fishing for salmon at Brooks Falls, explore the Valley of Ten Thousand Smokes, or hike along remote trails to experience the park\'s breathtaking scenery and abundant wildlife. With its untamed beauty and unparalleled opportunities for bear viewing and outdoor adventure, Katmai National Park offers a truly wild and unforgettable experience in the Alaskan wilderness.</string>
    <string name="Kenai_Fjords_National_Park_Description">Kenai Fjords National Park, located in Alaska, features towering glaciers, pristine fjords, and rugged coastline carved by ancient ice. Visitors can explore the park\'s dramatic landscapes on boat tours, kayak excursions, or hikes along scenic trails, witnessing calving glaciers, breaching whales, and abundant wildlife along the way. With its stunning natural beauty and opportunities for adventure, Kenai Fjords National Park offers a unique and unforgettable experience in the Last Frontier.</string>
    <string name="Kings_Canyon_National_Park_Description">Kings Canyon National Park, nestled in the Sierra Nevada mountains of California, is known for its deep canyons, towering sequoia trees, and majestic granite cliffs. Visitors can hike through groves of giant sequoias, explore scenic overlooks along the Kings Canyon Scenic Byway, or backpack into the park\'s rugged backcountry to experience its remote wilderness. With its breathtaking vistas, diverse ecosystems, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, Kings Canyon National Park offers a memorable escape into the beauty of the High Sierra.</string>
    <string name="Kobuk_Valley_National_Park_Description">Kobuk Valley National Park, located in northwest Alaska, is a remote wilderness of sand dunes, boreal forests, and caribou migration routes. Visitors can explore the park\'s vast landscapes on backpacking trips, river floats, or wildlife viewing excursions, encountering ancient archaeological sites, migrating caribou herds, and pristine wilderness along the way. With its untouched beauty and sense of solitude, Kobuk Valley National Park offers a truly wild and immersive experience in the Alaskan wilderness.</string>
    <string name="Lake_Clark_National_Park_and_Preserve_Description">Lake Clark National Park and Preserve, situated in southcentral Alaska, encompasses a diverse landscape of towering mountains, turquoise lakes, and coastal fjords. Visitors can explore the park\'s rugged terrain on hiking trails, rafting trips, or bear viewing excursions, encountering abundant wildlife such as brown bears, moose, and salmon along the way. With its stunning natural beauty and opportunities for outdoor adventure, Lake Clark National Park offers a remote and pristine escape into the heart of the Alaska Range.</string>
    <string name="Lassen_Volcanic_National_Park_Description">Lassen Volcanic National Park, located in northern California, showcases a volcanic landscape of steaming fumaroles, bubbling mud pots, and rugged peaks. Visitors can explore the park\'s geothermal wonders on hiking trails, scenic drives, or ranger-led programs, experiencing the power and beauty of the earth\'s geological forces. With its diverse ecosystems, stunning vistas, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, Lassen Volcanic National Park offers a fascinating journey into the dynamic world of volcanic activity.</string>
    <string name="Mammoth_Cave_National_Park_Description">Mammoth Cave National Park, situated in Kentucky, is home to the world\'s longest known cave system, with over 400 miles of explored passageways and chambers. Visitors can explore the park\'s underground wonders on guided cave tours, hike through scenic woodlands and river valleys, or camp in the park\'s campgrounds and backcountry areas. With its labyrinthine caves, lush forests, and rich history, Mammoth Cave National Park offers a fascinating journey into the hidden world beneath the surface of the earth.</string>
    <string name="Mesa_Verde_National_Park_Description">Mesa Verde National Park, located in southwestern Colorado, preserves ancient Puebloan cliff dwellings and archaeological sites dating back over 1,000 years. Visitors can explore the park\'s well-preserved ruins on ranger-led tours, hike along scenic trails that wind through the park\'s rugged canyons, or learn about the culture and history of the ancestral Puebloans at the park\'s visitor center and museum. With its rich cultural heritage, stunning landscapes, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, Mesa Verde National Park offers a captivating glimpse into the lives of ancient civilizations.</string>
    <string name="Mount_Rainier_National_Park_Description">Mount Rainier National Park, situated in Washington state, is dominated by the towering peak of Mount Rainier, an active stratovolcano and the tallest mountain in the Cascade Range. Visitors can explore the park\'s alpine meadows, old-growth forests, and glaciers on hiking trails, scenic drives, or ranger-led programs, experiencing the park\'s diverse ecosystems and breathtaking vistas. With its iconic mountain scenery, abundant wildlife, and opportunities for outdoor adventure, Mount Rainier National Park offers a memorable escape into the beauty of the Pacific Northwest.</string>
    <string name="New_River_Gorge_National_Park_and_Preserve_Description">New River Gorge National Park and Preserve, located in West Virginia, encompasses a rugged and scenic river canyon carved by the New River, one of the oldest rivers in the world. Visitors can explore the park\'s dramatic landscapes on hiking trails, whitewater rafting trips, or rock climbing excursions, encountering breathtaking vistas, diverse wildlife, and rich cultural history along the way. With its towering cliffs, rushing rapids, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, New River Gorge National Park and Preserve offers an exhilarating adventure in the heart of the Appalachian Mountains.</string>
    <string name="North_Cascades_National_Park_Description">North Cascades National Park, situated in northern Washington state, is known for its rugged mountains, cascading waterfalls, and pristine wilderness. Visitors can explore the park\'s remote backcountry on hiking trails, backpacking trips, or scenic drives along the North Cascades Highway, experiencing the park\'s diverse ecosystems and breathtaking scenery. With its towering peaks, alpine lakes, and abundant wildlife, North Cascades National Park offers a tranquil escape into the beauty of the Pacific Northwest.</string>
    <string name="Olympic_National_Park_Description">Olympic National Park, located in Washington state, is renowned for its diverse ecosystems, including rugged coastlines, temperate rainforests, and alpine meadows. Visitors can explore the park\'s scenic landscapes on hiking trails, enjoy beachcombing along the Pacific coast, or venture into the heart of the Hoh Rainforest to marvel at towering trees draped in moss. With its stunning natural beauty, rich biodiversity, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, Olympic National Park offers a memorable experience in the wild and remote landscapes of the Pacific Northwest.</string>
    <string name="Petrified_Forest_National_Park_Description">Petrified Forest National Park, situated in northeastern Arizona, preserves one of the largest and most colorful concentrations of petrified wood in the world, as well as ancient fossils and Native American ruins. Visitors can explore the park\'s unique landscapes on scenic drives, hike along trails that wind through petrified wood forests, or learn about the park\'s geological and cultural history at the visitor center and museum. With its fascinating geological formations, ancient artifacts, and stark desert scenery, Petrified Forest National Park offers a glimpse into the ancient past of the American Southwest.</string>
    <string name="Pinnacles_National_Park_Description">Pinnacles National Park, located in central California, showcases dramatic rock formations, rugged canyons, and diverse wildlife in the Gabilan Mountains. Visitors can explore the park\'s unique landscapes on hiking trails, rock climb on its towering spires, or watch for California condors soaring overhead. With its stunning vistas, abundant wildflowers, and opportunities for outdoor adventure, Pinnacles National Park offers a memorable escape into the rugged beauty of the California countryside.</string>
    <string name="Redwood_National_and_State_Parks_Description">Redwood National and State Parks, situated along the northern California coast, protect some of the tallest and oldest trees on Earth, the coast redwoods. Visitors can explore the park\'s towering forests on scenic drives, hike along trails that wind through ancient groves, or camp in campgrounds surrounded by towering trees. With its majestic redwoods, pristine coastline, and diverse ecosystems, Redwood National and State Parks offer a tranquil retreat into the heart of the California wilderness.</string>
    <string name="Rocky_Mountain_National_Park_Description">Rocky Mountain National Park, located in Colorado, is known for its soaring peaks, alpine lakes, and abundant wildlife. Visitors can explore the park\'s scenic landscapes on hiking trails, drive along the iconic Trail Ridge Road, or go wildlife watching for elk, bighorn sheep, and moose. With its stunning vistas, diverse ecosystems, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, Rocky Mountain National Park offers an unforgettable adventure in the heart of the Colorado Rockies.</string>
    <string name="Saguaro_National_Park_Description">Saguaro National Park, situated in southern Arizona, protects vast stands of towering saguaro cacti, as well as diverse desert ecosystems. Visitors can explore the park\'s scenic landscapes on hiking trails, drive along scenic roads that wind through cactus forests, or learn about the park\'s natural and cultural history at the visitor center and museum. With its iconic cacti, rugged mountains, and opportunities for outdoor adventure, Saguaro National Park offers a unique and unforgettable experience in the Sonoran Desert.</string>
    <string name="Sequoia_National_Park_Description">Sequoia National Park, located in California\'s Sierra Nevada mountains, is home to some of the largest and oldest trees on Earth, the giant sequoias. Visitors can explore the park\'s towering forests on hiking trails, marvel at the General Sherman Tree, the largest tree on Earth by volume, or drive through the famous Tunnel Log. With its majestic sequoias, scenic vistas, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, Sequoia National Park offers a memorable escape into the beauty of the California wilderness.</string>
    <string name="Shenandoah_National_Park_Description">Shenandoah National Park, situated in Virginia\'s Blue Ridge Mountains, offers stunning vistas, cascading waterfalls, and diverse wildlife. Visitors can explore the park\'s scenic landscapes on hiking trails, drive along the scenic Skyline Drive, or camp in campgrounds surrounded by lush forests. With its panoramic views, abundant wildflowers, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, Shenandoah National Park offers a tranquil retreat into the natural beauty of the Appalachian Mountains.</string>
    <string name="Theodore_Roosevelt_National_Park_Description">Theodore Roosevelt National Park, located in North Dakota, preserves the rugged badlands landscape that inspired President Theodore Roosevelt\'s conservation efforts. Visitors can explore the park\'s scenic landscapes on hiking trails, drive along scenic roads that wind through colorful rock formations, or learn about the park\'s natural and cultural history at the visitor center and museum. With its dramatic scenery, abundant wildlife, and opportunities for outdoor adventure, Theodore Roosevelt National Park offers a memorable journey into the heart of the American West.</string>
    <string name="Virgin_Islands_National_Park_Description">Virgin Islands National Park, located on the island of St. John in the U.S. Virgin Islands, encompasses pristine beaches, lush tropical forests, and vibrant coral reefs. Visitors can explore the park\'s scenic landscapes on hiking trails, snorkel or dive among colorful coral gardens, or relax on secluded beaches. With its crystal-clear waters, abundant marine life, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, Virgin Islands National Park offers a serene escape into the beauty of the Caribbean.</string>
    <string name="Voyageurs_National_Park_Description">Voyageurs National Park, situated in northern Minnesota, is a water-based wilderness of interconnected lakes, rivers, and forests. Visitors can explore the park\'s scenic waterways by canoe, kayak, or motorboat, camp on remote islands, or hike along trails that wind through the park\'s rugged terrain. With its pristine lakes, abundant wildlife, and opportunities for boating and fishing, Voyageurs National Park offers a peaceful retreat into the heart of the Northwoods.</string>
    <string name="White_Sands_National_Park_Description">
White Sands National Park, located in New Mexico, is a surreal landscape of gypsum sand dunes stretching across 275 square miles of desert terrain. The park\'s shimmering white sands create a stunning contrast against the deep blue skies, offering visitors a unique and otherworldly experience. Visitors can explore the dunes on hiking trails, sled down the sandy slopes, or marvel at the park\'s diverse plant and animal life adapted to this harsh environment. With its pristine beauty, serene atmosphere, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, White Sands National Park offers a mesmerizing escape into the heart of the Chihuahuan Desert.</string>
    <string name="Wind_Cave_National_Park_Description">Wind Cave National Park, located in South Dakota, features one of the world\'s longest and most complex cave systems, as well as vast grasslands and rolling hills. Visitors can explore the park\'s underground wonders on guided cave tours, hike through the park\'s scenic landscapes, or watch for bison, elk, and pronghorn on the prairie. With its unique geological features, diverse ecosystems, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, Wind Cave National Park offers a memorable adventure in the Great Plains.</string>
    <string name="WrangellSt._Elias_National_Park_and_Preserve_Description">Wrangell-St. Elias National Park and Preserve, situated in Alaska, is the largest national park in the United States, encompassing vast expanses of rugged mountains, glaciers, and wilderness. Visitors can explore the park\'s remote backcountry on backpacking trips, flightseeing tours, or rafting expeditions, encountering stunning vistas, abundant wildlife, and pristine wilderness along the way. With its towering peaks, icy rivers, and sense of solitude, Wrangell-St. Elias National Park and Preserve offers a truly epic adventure in the wild and remote landscapes of the Last Frontier.</string>
    <string name="Yellowstone_National_Park_Description">Yellowstone National Park, located primarily in Wyoming but also extending into Montana and Idaho, is famous for its geothermal features, including geysers, hot springs, and mud pots, as well as its diverse wildlife and stunning landscapes. Visitors can explore the park\'s iconic attractions, such as Old Faithful and the Grand Canyon of the Yellowstone, on scenic drives, hike along trails that wind through the park\'s diverse ecosystems, or watch for wolves, grizzly bears, and bison in the park\'s wildlife-rich habitats. With its natural wonders, abundant wildlife, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, Yellowstone National Park offers an unforgettable experience in the heart of the American West.</string>
    <string name="Yosemite_National_Park_Description">Yosemite National Park, situated in California\'s Sierra Nevada mountains, is renowned for its towering granite cliffs, majestic waterfalls, and ancient sequoia trees. Visitors can explore the park\'s iconic landmarks, such as Half Dome and Yosemite Falls, on hiking trails, rock climb on its legendary granite walls, or camp in the park\'s scenic campgrounds. With its breathtaking vistas, diverse ecosystems, and opportunities for outdoor adventure, Yosemite National Park offers a memorable escape into the beauty of the California wilderness.</string>
    <string name="Zion_National_Park_Description">Zion National Park, located in southern Utah, is characterized by its towering sandstone cliffs, narrow slot canyons, and lush river valleys. Visitors can explore the park\'s scenic landscapes on hiking trails, drive along the Zion-Mount Carmel Highway, or take a scenic shuttle ride through the Zion Canyon Scenic Drive. With its stunning vistas, diverse ecosystems, and opportunities for outdoor recreation, Zion National Park offers a memorable adventure in the heart of the American Southwest.</string>
    <string name="navigate_back">Navigate back</string>


</resources>